{
    "id": "84356ebc81614ac0a84436cd5a0657cf",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is only putting .............................. an act.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "04c289fd6c62465d95793fd7b13386fa"
        },
        {
            "question": "We chatted ........................................ for over an hour.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "761963d2273c4cfab5c573590a254fdf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am sick .............................. the whole business.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "up",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b5bda5e5e63946af9c06514758b37597"
        },
        {
            "question": "Put the money ................................., you may need it later.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "by",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ceb19794e02a41e7a7aa9042cc7f1258"
        },
        {
            "question": "The vicar told me I could practice ............................... the organ.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b3aa10cbdf4a4a7294344724efce29e4"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a catch .................................. it somewhere.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "330eaee8a33b4d6eb78feeb9b87c1b5d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge let him ..................................... with a caution.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5da06815173d4b54a967d223d114f946"
        },
        {
            "question": "It came .................................... a lot of money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fb7359487abf4aeab4d3c746596c680e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The thief was condemned ................................... gaol.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d4ed001acf2478ba826e2ed24a15fe3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly a bright idea dawned .................................. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b7bfbfb23b824f07b5490e212dc858af"
        }
    ]
}